ANTONIO BRITO

COMPUTER PROGRAMMER

CONTACT

Mobile: (519) 859-2686

Email: antubritov@gmail.com

Address: 22924 Valleyview Road

Thorndale, ON, Canada

N0M2P0

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

Oracle Forms versions 4.0, 4.5, 6,

6i, 9i, 10g,11g, 12c.

Oracle Reports versions 4.0, 4.5, 6,

6i, 9i, 10g,11g, 12c.

Oracle Database

PL/SQL Oracle

C++ & Java

MongoDB & Firebase

HTML & CSS

SOFTWARE

Toad &SQL Developer

Git

Visual Studio, Eclipse, WebStorm

Photoshop, Illustrator

Phone Gap (Mobile Tool)

Autosys.

METHODOLOGY

Waterfall

Agile Methodology (Kanban)

PROFILE 2

Participated in some phases of software development life cycle including requirements, design, development, testing, implementation, maintenance, and troubleshooting.

Involved in the support, maintenance, and development of critical systems, providing answers and solutions to systems problem errors.

 Coding with IOS application development using XCODE (using Storyboard) and SWIFT.

Created Oracle objects e.g., tables, views, index, stored procedures, functions, packages, and triggers.

Defining and generating screen formats and report design in Oracle.

Developing in accordance with policies, secure coding & standards.

Meeting clients to ascertain requirement for computer system modules.

Developing software in accordance with agreed design with consideration for usability, software quality and future maintenance.

Experienced in Oracle programming and working with software development

EDUCATION 😂

Fanshawe College

Graduated 2019

Computer Programming Analyst - Advanced Diploma

Costa Rica Institute of Technology

Graduated 2002

Master (Honors) in Computer System Information

Honorific Award for Best Software Invention. (Auditory perception software for kindergarten kids).

Oracle Costa Rica Corporation

2000

Training in Oracle Forms, Reports, PL/SQL and Database management.

Costa Rica Institute of Technology

Graduated 1998

Bachelors in information systems.

antubritov@gmail.com

LANGUAGES

Spanish (Mother Tongue)

English Fluent

CERTIFICATES

Internet Business Application
Ecommerce, SK Telecom

(South Korea).

Oracle Costa Rica Forms, Reports, PL/SQL., Toad

Advance Course on Multimedia
& Web design. Centre for
Electronics Design & Technology
of India.

Advance English
Berkeley University.
California, USA.

INTERESTS

- Sports / Fitness
- Travelling

EXPERIENCE

TD Canada Trust, IT Support. London, On

September 2019 – Now

- Handle, troubleshoot and resolve incidents in the different applications environments including Production.
- Provide support to audit teams for the finding of unlocated differences as well as the creation of several reports.
- Access mainframe to search for data and execute processes.
- Assist in the upgrade of configuration packages for API's.
- Creation of multiple technical manuals with specific steps to follow for the solution of recurrent incidents.
- Support new colleagues and coop students during initial setup.
- Creation and maintenance of passwords of the different applications using CyberArk tool.

TD Canada Trust, (CO-OP) London, On

Jan 2019 - Apr 2019

- Executed daily, weekly and monthly reports required by other teams.
- Researched and analyzed how to capture errors when running job scheduler
- Executed batch scripts
- Team support

TD Canada Trust, (CO-OP) London, On

May 2018 - Sep 2018

- Developed a Java application to compare and find inconsistencies in the TFSA files.
- Created full documentation as to how to use above application.
- Updated Confluence page for the Investment team.
- Involvement and team support (Cobol, SQL)

STEP NETWORKS, (CO-OP) London, On

Sep 2017 - Jan 2018

- Fixed bugs and coded on a system aimed towards insurance.
- Developed a mobile services control system application using XCODE and SWIFT.
- Coded several modules for the mobile application including, clients, equipment, schedule jobs, hours, using interfaces, tableviews and storyboards.
- Implemented full CRUD functionality on modules using SQL Lite as Database.

Oracle Software Consultant, Support and Developer S, Costa Rica Jan 2000 – Dec 2014

- Interview, collect, coding and testing new user system requirements.
- Create data base model scripts for every project with the software development team.
- Coding new projects using Oracle forms and reports in accordance with policies, secure coding & company standards.
- Provided training for new system modules to employees.
- Participated in weekly staff meetings and software team meetings to analyze project system requirements and development advances.
- Solving system problems, identifying system "bugs" from user's concerns and implementing a better solution for any software banking modules (Customer Accounts, Financial Accounting, Teller (Cash), Payments, Deposits, and Loans).
- Writing relevant documentation for user requirement tests, specifications and reviewing it with them.
- Developed an informative internal web page, including designs.